[{"answer": " Hi, Grandpa.  Are you ready to try to use a computer", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Carla, I dont know about this.  Why in the world does an old man like m", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Hi, Grandpa.  Are you ready to try to use a computer", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Grandpa, we talked about this.  You can email people and look things up on th", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Carla, I dont know about this.  Why in the world does an old man like m", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " My typewriter is broken.  I guess youre right.  Ill try the computer", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Grandpa, we talked about this.  You can email people and look things up on th", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Good.  Youll see. Its so user-friendly.  Youll have no problem", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " My typewriter is broken.  I guess youre right.  Ill try the computer", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": "All right.  Ill give it a shot", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Good.  Youll see. Its so user-friendly.  Youll have no problem", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " OK.  This is the power button.  The first thing you have to do is press this to tur", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 25, "question": "All right.  Ill give it a shot", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 29, "question": " OK.  This is the power button.  The first thing you have to do is press this to tur", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " When you see this screen, you can choose what application you want to open", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 33, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Whats an application, honey", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 34, "question": " When you see this screen, you can choose what application you want to open", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Oh, thats computer talk.  It means a program on the computer.  Like there is ", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Whats an application, honey", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " All right.  I see", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Oh, thats computer talk.  It means a program on the computer.  Like there is ", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Now you see this little W icon here", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 41, "question": " All right.  I see", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Uh-huh, I see it", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Now you see this little W icon here", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Well, you use the mouse to double-click on it.  See", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Uh-huh, I see it", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " So I click two times on it", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Well, you use the mouse to double-click on it.  See", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Thats right.  Any time you double-click, you open something up", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " So I click two times on it", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Thats right.  Any time you double-click, you open something up", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Now, see.  That opened up the Word program.  Now you can start typing here i", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Well, thats not too hard", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Now, see.  That opened up the Word program.  Now you can start typing here i", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " No, its pretty easy.  I told you.  The thing you have to remember is that you nee", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Well, thats not too hard", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Well, how do I do that", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 56, "question": " No, its pretty easy.  I told you.  The thing you have to remember is that you nee", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " See this word File at the top", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Well, how do I do that", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Yes", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 58, "question": " See this word File at the top", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Well, you click on that and it brings up a menu.  Then, you click on Save As", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Yes", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Id better write that down", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Well, you click on that and it brings up a menu.  Then, you click on Save As", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Ill write it all down for you Grandpa.  I just want to show you now", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Id better write that down", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " OK, sure.  Thank you", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Ill write it all down for you Grandpa.  I just want to show you now", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Now if you write anything important, youll also want to save a back-up copy", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 69, "question": " OK, sure.  Thank you", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " That sounds pretty complicated", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Now if you write anything important, youll also want to save a back-up copy", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " No, its easy too.  You can just save it to a disk.  Ill show you that another da", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 74, "question": " That sounds pretty complicated", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Yeah, this is already a lot to learn.  Hey, whats that picture on the scree", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 76, "question": " No, its easy too.  You can just save it to a disk.  Ill show you that another da", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Thats called a screen saver, grandpa.  If you dont use the computer for a fe", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Yeah, this is already a lot to learn.  Hey, whats that picture on the scree", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Well, how beautiful", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Thats called a screen saver, grandpa.  If you dont use the computer for a fe", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " I guess.  We can put a picture of you and me as your screen saver", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Well, how beautiful", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Well, thatd be nice", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 90, "question": " I guess.  We can put a picture of you and me as your screen saver", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " So, thats probably enough to show you for today.  Dont you think Grandpa", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Well, thatd be nice", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " I think so.   Let me practice what youve shown me and then Ill learn som", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 92, "question": " So, thats probably enough to show you for today.  Dont you think Grandpa", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " You may be 75, but you can learn to use it Grandpa", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 94, "question": " I think so.   Let me practice what youve shown me and then Ill learn som", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Well see", "docId": "02-09", "aSentId": 95, "question": " You may be 75, but you can learn to use it Grandpa", "qSentId": 94}]
